One look give ‘em Whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash
C'mon, focus
Fokuskan lagi, lebih fokuskan
集中して もっと
집중해 좀 더
มีสมาธิมากขึ้นหน่อย
再集中一点
再更集中一些
Hãy tập trung hơn nữa
Think fast
They're reasons you'll never understand
Itulah alasan kau tak akan bisa mengerti
理由 君には分からない
이유 넌 이해 못 해
เธอคงไม่เข้าใจเหตุผล
理由你不会明白
理由你無法理解
Anh không hiểu được nguyên nhân đâu
Why at last
Mengapa sekarang
どうして今さら
왜 이제야
ทำไมต้องตอนนี้
为什么现在才
怎麼到現在才
Tại sao tới bây giờ
Know I did that
Day 1 know I been bad
Don’t stop
Still shook
Meski tergoyang
搖さぶられたまま
흔들린 채
แม้จะสั่นไหว
摇摆不定
搖搖擺擺
Trong trạng thái rung động
Goin' too hard, yet
Dan berlebihan
無理しても
무리해도
และหักโหมมากไปก็ตาม
勉强为之
就算勉強
Dù có cố bao nhiêu
Can’t touch that (Can't touch that)
Under pressure,
body sweating
Can you focus
Wherever I am can't stop me
Tak dapat dihentikan di mana pun
どこでだってためらわずに
어디서나 거침없어
ไม่ว่าจะที่ไหน ก็ไม่ลังเล
无论在哪里都无所顾忌
無論在哪都勇往直前
Đi đâu cũng không ai ngăn được
I’m the coldest
I'm the only
Akulah satu-satunya
ただ私だけが
오직 나만이
มีเพียงฉันคนเดียวเท่านั้น
唯有我是
只有我是
Chỉ có một mình em
Game-Changer bringin' the new era
Changer yang mengubah permainan ini
この構圖を變える Changer
이 판을 바꿀 Changer
Changer ที่เปลี่ยนเกมนี้ได้
颠覆这局面的 Changer
將改變局面的 Changer
Là Changer lật đổ tình huống
Just close your eyes,
breathe in and visualize
One look give ‘em Whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash
C'mon, focus
Fokuskan lagi, lebih fokuskan
集中して もっと
집중해 좀 더
มีสมาธิมากขึ้นหน่อย
再集中一点
再更集中一些
Hãy tập trung hơn nữa
Think fast
They're reasons you'll never understand
Itulah alasan kau tak akan bisa mengerti
理由 君には分からない
이유 넌 이해 못 해
เธอคงไม่เข้าใจเหตุผล
理由你不会明白
理由你無法理解
Anh không hiểu được nguyên nhân đâu
Why at last
Mengapa sekarang
どうして今さら
왜 이제야
ทำไมต้องตอนนี้
为什么现在才
怎麼到現在才
Tại sao tới bây giờ
Know I did that
Day 1 know I been bad
Don’t stop
Still shook
Meski tergoyang
搖さぶられたまま
흔들린 채
แม้จะสั่นไหว
摇摆不定
搖搖擺擺
Trong trạng thái rung động
Goin' too hard, yet
Dan berlebihan
無理しても
무리해도
และหักโหมมากไปก็ตาม
勉强为之
就算勉強
Dù có cố bao nhiêu
Can’t touch that
(Can't touch that)
Whip-Whiplash
One look give ‘em Whiplash
Fancy
This so glitzy
Ini benar-benar mewah
これって本當派手だね
이건 참 화려해
นี่มันหรูหรางดงามมาก
这个真的很华丽
這太華麗
Thật là lộng lẫy
It’s glowing and it’s flashy
Keep it just right, I know it
Aku tahu apa itu cukup
分かってる 適度とは何か
알아 적당함이 뭔지
รู้ว่าสิ่งที่เหมาะสมคืออะไร
我明白什么是恰如其分
我知道什麼是恰到好處
Em biết thế nào là vừa phải
Keep it classy
Cats gon' copy
Menirunya
マネする
따라 하지
เธอทำตามฉัน
跟着效仿
我照著做
Lại bắt chước
One idea, two, then the whole look
Dari satu sampai sepuluh, kamu
君はまた一から十まで
넌 또 하나부터 열까지
ตั้งแต่หนึ่งถึงสิบ
你又从一到十
你又從頭到尾
Lại từ đầu đến cuối
Then deny it Yeah
pura-pura tidak tahu Yeah
白を切る Yeah
아닌척하지 Yeah
แล้วแกล้งทำเป็นไม่ใช่ Yeah
装作若无其事 Yeah
裝得若無其事 Yeah
Giả vờ không biết gì Yeah
Under pressure,
body sweating
Can you focus (Hoo)
I deliver, I can promise
I’m the coldest
(Cold)
Head in the sand won't solve it
Tak ada gunanya beralih muka
無視しても無馱だよ
외면해도 소용없지
หันไปก็ไม่มีประโยชน์
回避也无济于事
想逃避也沒有用
Dù có lờ đi cũng vô ích
Don't you blow it
Just close your eyes,
breathe in and visualize
The moment it begins
Saat itu dimulai
始まる瞬間
시작되는 순간
ณ จุดที่เริ่มต้น
开始的瞬间
在開始的瞬間
Khoảnh khắc bắt đầu
Verdict is in
Penilaian yang berakhir
終わってしまった判斷
끝나버린 판단
การตัดสินที่สิ้นสุดแล้ว
结束的判断
判斷就已結束
Phán đoán đã kết thúc
Opportunity knocks just One time
Kesempatannya hanya One time
チャンスはたった One time
기횐 오직 One time
มีแต่โอกาส One time
机会只有 One time
機會只有 One time
Cơ hội chỉ có One time
Unforgettable
I found The right light
The right light yang ditemukan
見つけ出した The right light
찾아낸 The right light
The right light ที่จะพบ
找到的 The right light
Đã tìm ra The right light
Won't go gentle into the night
Takkan hilang
消えない
사라지지 않아
มันจะไม่หายไป
不会就此消失
不會消失
Sẽ không biến mất đâu
Etched in my eyes One time
One time yang terukir di mataku
目に燒き付けた One time
눈에 새긴 One time
One time ที่ตราตรึงอยู่ในดวงตาของฉัน
刻在眼里的 One time
刻在眼裡的 One time
Ghi dấu ấn trong mắt One time
Unforgettable
One look give ‘em Whiplash
Beat drop with a big flash
C'mon, focus
Fokuskan lagi, lebih fokuskan
集中して もっと
집중해 좀 더
มีสมาธิมากขึ้นหน่อย
再集中一点
再更集中一些
Hãy tập trung hơn nữa
Think fast
They're reasons you'll never understand
Itulah alasan kau tak akan bisa mengerti
理由 君には分からない
이유 넌 이해 못 해
เธอคงไม่เข้าใจเหตุผล
理由你不会明白
理由你無法理解
Anh không hiểu được nguyên nhân đâu
Why at last
Mengapa sekarang
どうして今さら
왜 이제야
ทำไมต้องตอนนี้
为什么现在才
怎麼到現在才
Tại sao tới bây giờ
Know I did that
Day 1 know I been bad
Don’t stop
Still shook
Meski tergoyang
揺さぶられたまま
흔들린 채
แม้จะสั่นไหว
摇摆不定
搖搖擺擺
Trong trạng thái rung động
Goin' too hard, yet
Dan berlebihan
無理しても
무리해도
และหักโหมมากไปก็ตาม
勉强为之
就算勉強
Dù có cố bao nhiêu
Can’t touch that
(Can't touch that)
I’m the highlight
Shine the Red light
Menyinari Red light
照らす Red light
비춰 Red light
ส่องสว่าง Red light
照射 Red light
照著 Red light
Chiếu sáng Red light
Yeah Tonight,
it's all about me
(All about me)
You know it’s my site
Next sigh so heavy
Next sigh yang berat
荒い Next sigh
거친 Next sigh
Next sigh ที่รุนแรง
粗重的 Next sigh
Thô thiển Next sigh
We be writin' History
History yang akan aku buat
作っていく History
만들어갈 History
History ที่จะสร้างขึ้น
将创造的 History
將寫下的 History
History sẽ viết lên
One look give ‘em Whiplash (Whip-Whip)
Beat drop with a big flash
C'mon keep up, Move fast (Move move move)
Ikuti aku, ayo Move fast (Move move move)
ついてきて 早く Move fast (Move move move)
따라와 어서 Move fast (Move move move)
ตามมาเร็วๆสิ Move fast (Move move move)
快跟上吧 Move fast (Move move move)
Hãy theo em nhanh lên Move fast (Move move move)
They're reasons you'll never understand
Itulah alasan kau tak akan bisa mengerti
理由 君には分からない
이유 넌 이해 못 해
เธอคงไม่เข้าใจเหตุผล
理由你不会明白
理由你無法理解
Anh không hiểu được nguyên nhân đâu
Why at last
Mengapa sekarang
どうして今さら
왜 이제야
ทำไมต้องตอนนี้
为什么现在才
怎麼到現在才
Tại sao tới bây giờ
Know I did that (Did that)
Day 1 know I been bad (Been bad)
Don’t stop
Still shook
Meski tergoyang
搖さぶられたまま
흔들린 채
แม้จะสั่นไหว
摇摆不定
搖搖擺擺
Trong trạng thái rung động
Even it be incomin'
Meski mendekati
近づいてきても
다가와도
และหักโหมมากไปก็ตาม
即使靠近
Dù có theo em
Can’t touch that
(Can't touch that)
Whip-Whiplash
One look give ‘em Whiplash